excellentpools.info 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Excellent PoolsExcellent Pools

You are here: [Home](http://excellentpools.info/) / Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for excellentpools.info**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at hello@myadress.com.

At excellentpools.info, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by excellentpools.info and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, excellentpools.info makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
excellentpools.info does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on excellentpools.info.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to excellentpools.info and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on excellentpools.info send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

excellentpools.info has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. excellentpools.info’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

Every instance of user access to a page of this website as well as every download of a file will result in a record of the procedure being made in a protocol file. These data are non-personalised, i.e. it cannot be determined which user accessed or retrieved which data. The following data will be stored for each instance of access or retrieval: name of the accessed/retrieved file, date and time of access/retrieval, volume of data transferred and a report on the success of the access/retrieval.

This website employs Google Analytics with the extension “_anonymizeIp()” and therefore IP addresses will only be processed in reduced form, in order to prevent the identification of individual persons.

With the exception of Google Analytics (see next paragraph), this website employs no cookies which could conceivably be used to trace the accessing behaviour of users.

**Google Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc.

Google Analytics uses so called “cookies”, text files which are saved on the users computer and enable an analysis of the usage of the platform through the user. The information that the cookie generates about a user’s activity on this website is normally transferred to and stored on a server operated by Google in the USA.

IP address anonymisation is activated on this website resulting in the abbreviation by Google of IP addresses within member states of the European Union and contracting parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional circumstances will a complete IP address be transferred to a Google server in the USA and subsequently abbreviated.

On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will process this information in order to evaluate use of the website, to produce reports concerning the website activities and to produce additional services associated with the use of the internet and website. The IP address of a user’s browser determined by Google Analytics will not be combined with any other data held by Google.

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

In addition, you can prevent the compilation and processing of data generated by cookies regarding your use of this website (including your IP address) by downlaoding and installing the following browser plug-in.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
